http://www.hypermed.com/privacy-policy

HomeThe NeedThe SolutionProductCompanyNewsContact
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how HyperMed Imaging, Inc. collects the personal information of the users of this website (“Users”), how HyperMed Imaging, Inc. uses and protects that information, and what you can do to help protect that information. If you have any additional questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
HyperMed Imaging, Inc. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.
HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective beginning 10/01/2016.
To effectively operate the website, HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may from time to time collect and use personally identifiable information. This personally identifiable information may include your name and job title, contact information including email addresses, and demographic information such as postal code (“Personal Information”). We collect this information to understand your needs and contact you with information that may be of interest to you, and to improve our products and services. You may email HyperMed Imaging, Inc. at [info@hypermed.com] to find out what Personal Information about you has been collected, and to request changes to your Personal Information.
In addition, the website automatically collects anonymous information about Users. For example, the website automatically gathers a User’s Internet Protocol address, which Internet Service Provider the User utilizes, statistics about how Users navigate through and use the Site, and information gathered through the use of “cookies.” A “cookie” is a piece of data stored on the User’s computer tied to information about the User. HyperMed Imaging, Inc. uses cookies and the other anonymous information to maintain the quality of the Services, help HyperMed Imaging, Inc. understand how Users choose the website, and to know when Users have accessed the website from a paid advertiser, an affiliate website, or a strategic partner website. HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may also compile statistics that track the usage of the website. These statistics are used for internal purposes only and contain no Personal Information.
Solely for the purposes of confirming valid traffic from certain pay-per-click search engines, IP addresses for Users may be monitored, and may be compared to the records of that search engine.
How HyperMed Imaging, Inc. responds to “Do Not Track” signals: At this time the website does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies may affect your online experience and may prevent you from using all of the features of the website. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.
HyperMed Imaging, Inc. works to protect the security of Personal Information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that is transmitted on the website. HyperMed Imaging, Inc. uses the Personal Information of a User to provide services to the User, and to respond to customer service or support questions. HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may employ companies and individuals to perform functions on HyperMed Imaging, Inc.’s behalf. Examples may include providing marketing assistance, performing statistical analysis, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to the Personal Information only as necessary to perform their functions, and may not access or use it for any other purpose. If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your Personal Information by HyperMed Imaging, Inc. to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [info@hypermed.com].
HyperMed Imaging, Inc. has appropriate security measures in place within its database and physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that has been collected on the website. These measures include limiting the number of people who have physical access to HyperMed Imaging, Inc.’s database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access. However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.
HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may utilize e-mail to communicate with Users. HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may also occasionally use a User’s Personal Information to notify the User of HyperMed Imaging, Inc.’s products and services via periodic mailings or e-mail updates. Users may opt-out of these communications by emailing HyperMed Imaging, Inc. at [info@hypermed.com] with “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line.
HyperMed Imaging, Inc. will not sell Personal Information of any User. However, in the event HyperMed Imaging, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger or an acquisition of its equity interests or assets, the Personal Information of Users will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) imposes restrictions on commercial websites, including ours. It is our policy to be compliant with the requirements of COPPA and not to solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13 (“Child”) without parent or guardian consent. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a Child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers.
Although HyperMed Imaging, Inc. makes every effort to preserve User privacy, HyperMed Imaging, Inc. may need to disclose or provide access to Personal Information if HyperMed Imaging, Inc. has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with the law, such as in connection with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process.
Users that have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy should contact HyperMed Imaging, Inc. by email at [info@hypermed.com].
HyperMed’s new tissue oximetry device called HyperView™ is FDA 510(k) cleared.HyperMed, HyperView, OxyVu™-1 and the company logo are trademarks of HyperMed Imaging, Inc.
HomeThe NeedThe SolutionProductCompanyNewsContact
